suspension: n.   悬，吊
Lesson 17, the longest suspension, bridge in the world,
第17课，最长的悬架，世界上的桥梁，
Verisano, an Italian about whom little is known,
verisano，一个鲜为人知的意大利语，
sailed into New York Harbor in 1524 and named it on Gilem.
1524年，航行到纽约港，并在吉利姆（Gilem）命名。
agreeable: adj. 宜人的, situation: n.   地点，地方
He described it as a very agreeable situation
他形容这是一个非常令人愉快的情况
locate: v.   位于
located within two small hills in the midst of which.
位于其中的两个小山丘中。
Float a great river, though Verisano is by no means considered to be a great explorer.
浮动一条大河，尽管Verisano绝不是一位伟大的探险家。
immortal: adj. 永生的，流芳百世的
His name will probably remain immortal.
他的名字可能会不朽。
suspension: n.   悬，吊
For on November 21st, 1964, the longest suspension bridge in the world was named after him.
对于1964年11月21日，世界上最长的悬架桥以他的名字命名。
The Verisano bridge, which was designed by Othmar Amman,
由奥斯玛·安曼（Othmar Ammann）设计的Verrazano桥
Brooklyn: n.   布鲁克林（纽约一区名）, Staten: n.   斯塔顿（岛）
joins Brooklyn to Staten Island.
加入布鲁克林到史坦顿岛。
span: n.   跨度
It has a span of 4,260 feet.
它的跨度为4,260英尺。
The bridge is so long that the shape of the earth had to be taken into account by its designer.
桥梁太长了，以至于地球的形状必须由其设计师考虑在内。
cable: n.   缆索
Two great towers support four huge cables.
两座很棒的塔楼支撑着四根大电缆。
concrete: n.   混凝土
The towers are built on immense underwater platforms make of steel and concrete.
这些塔楼建在巨大的水下平台上，由钢和混凝土制成。
The platforms extend to a depth of over 100 feet under the sea.
这些平台延伸到海底以上100英尺的深度。
These alone took 16 months to build.
仅这些就需要16个月才能建造。
Above the surface of the water, the towers rise to a height of nearly 700 feet.
在水面上方，塔楼上升到近700英尺的高度。
cable: n.   缆索, suspend: v.   悬挂
They support the cables from which the bridge has been suspended.
他们支撑桥被悬挂的电缆。
cable: n.   缆索, length: n.   根，段
Each of the four cables contains 26,108 lengths of wire.
这四根电缆中的每根都包含26,108条电线。
estimate: v.   估计
It has been estimated that if the bridge were packed with cars,
据估计，如果桥上装满了汽车，
capacity: n.   承受量
it would still only be carrying a third of its total capacity.
它仍然只有其总容量的三分之一。
However, size and strength are not the only important things about this bridge.
但是，大小和强度并不是这座桥的唯一重要事情。
immensity: n.   巨大, elegant: adj. 优美别致的
Despite its immensity, it is both simple and elegant, fulfilling its designer's dream to create
尽管它很大，但它既简单又优雅，实现了设计师的梦想
faintly: adv. 微细地
an enormous object drawn as faintly as possible.
尽可能微弱地绘制的巨大物体。